trovit.co.in 2017-06-26

# Privacy policy - Trovit Corporate

This Privacy Policy was originally published in Spanish and translated to other languages for informative reasons and to facilitate its consultation. In case of a discrepancy between this version and the [spanish version](http://corporate.trovit.com/politica-de-privacidad/) of this Privacy Policy, the Spanish version shall prevail and shall be used to the effects of interpretation and/or application.

This Privacy Policy is applicable to all the services offered via www.trovit.es (hereinafter, the “Web Site” or “Portal) by TROVIT SEARCH, S.L with VAT number B-64342454 and registered address at Avenida Diagonal, 601, P. 9, 08028, Barcelona (hereinafter “Trovit”).

We inform you that the data that you provide us when you access to and use each of the services offered through the Web Site will be added to a file which is duly registered at the General Registry of the Spanish Data Protection Agency under the responsibility of Trovit, and will be processed with the purposes described below:

* **myTrovit**

Trovit will process your data with the purpose of registering you in the service, allowing you to create a Trovit profile. In order to register with this service, you must provide an e-mail address that will be linked with your registration account.

In order to be able to access to the other services offered through the Portal (alert service and MyCVs), you must previously have been registered in MyTrovit.

* **Alert Service**

Trovit will process your data for the purpose of sending you commercial information based on the personalised alerts that you have previously created. Thus, whenever Trovit finds a new advertisement which might be of your interest, you will receive a notification by e-mail.

Unless otherwise indicated in the check box enabled during the registration process, you give your express consent for the processing of your data by Trovit with the purpose of sending you commercial information (including electronic newsletter) on the services eventually offered by Trovit via postal mail, e-mail, SMS or any other equivalent means of electronic communication.

* **MyCVs Service**

Trovit will process your data with the following purposes:

a. Sending job offers suitable to your professional profile: if you have registered in the service linking your LinkedIn account or the professional network eventually specified, Trovit will access and store the information contained in your profile (full profile and e-mail address linked to the account). Additionally, Trovit will process your data with the purpose of showing you offers which may be of your interest based on the information contained in your LinkedIn profile or in the profile of the professional network you have registered with, as well as on any other information which you add to your registration account in accordance with section b. below

b. Applying for the jobs offered published by our clients on the Portal: in order to gain access to this service, the user must add his/her curriculum vitae to his/her registration account on the Web Site, and select those job offers that are of his/her interest. In these cases, Trovit will additionally process your personal data with the purpose of managing the delivery of your application to the company that has published the job offer that you have selected. 

We inform you that your data will be transferred to the company that has published the job offer with the purpose of handling and maintaining your application for available positions.

c. Allowing our clients to gain access to your information: if you have expressly granted your consent through the configuration of the privacy settings in your account, we inform you that the personal data that you have entered in the Portal will be accessible to our clients, who may look at them at any moment for the purpose of evaluating your eligibility for available positions.

Additionally, we inform you that we shall use your data to inform you of improvements, updates and new services or functions related to the MyCVs Service.

Unless otherwise specified, all the data that we request you during the registration process and through the forms available at the Portal are mandatory, so that the omission of any of them might involve the impossibility to provide you with the requested services. We request you to inform us immediately of any modification in your data so that the information contained in our files is updated at all times and does not contain any error. In this connection, you state that the information and the data that you provide are, at all times, accurate, up to date and true.

At any moment, you may exercise your access, cancellation, rectification or objection rights, on the terms set out in the personal data protection regulations by writing to the above-mentioned address or to the e-mail address info@trovit.com, enclosing a copy of your ID or equivalent official document.

Trovit will process your data at all times in an absolutely confidential manner and in accordance with the required duty of secrecy with regard to them, in accordance with the provisions of the applicable regulations, adopting for the purpose the measures of a technical and organisational nature that are necessary to guarantee the security of your data and prevent their alteration, loss, treatment or unauthorised access taking into account the state of technology, the nature of the data stored and the risks to which they are exposed.

Finally, we inform you that Trovit’s services are designed to be used by persons of over fourteen years of age. If you have not yet reached your fourteenth birthday, you cannot use these services or give Trovit any personal data. If you are aged between fourteen and eighteen, you state that you have looked through these terms and conditions with a parent or legal guardian and you state that both you and your parent or legal guardian understand the present privacy policy, as well as Trovit’s [General Conditions](http://corporate.trovit.com/terms-conditions/). If you are a parent or legal guardian and you permit a minor to use Trovit’s services, you undertake to: supervise the use made by the minor of Trovit’s services; (ii) accept all the risks associated with the use that the minor makes of the contents or other information received from the services, including the transfer of materials, contents or other information to and from third parties over the internet; (iii) accept the responsibility resulting from the use by the minor of Trovit’s services; and (iv) ensure that all the information sent by the minor is accurate, up to date and true.
